[Music]
So guys, the service is very bad
and I have experienced it myself, so right now
we are going to the showroom and see what
work has been done on our car and what has not been done, so
I will show you, I gave the car to them
a week ago, I had not made a video at that time,
but I thought that my work will be done,
then why should I make a video
unnecessarily, and now I have to make a video
because the service is
very third class, so we will go and talk about
what is there, what is there,
first of all guys, what do these people
say, their briefing is absolutely rubbish, I
mean, they will not entertain you at all
and will not even solve your query, you will have to stand in a
very long line for whatever problem you have, you
can see, there
is construction here, whatever stones etc. are falling from above,
all of them fall on the car,
look, I was searching for it in my car, where is it, I could not find it, guys,
these people had kept it in the front, the
condition of the front became even worse, there were
scratches on the tank also  I had come here, I would
say don't come at all, now the
service of these people is very worst, guys the review here is that it is
absolutely third
class, don't spoil your car at all,
what are you seeing by parking this guy, a building is being constructed here, due to which
whatever stone, cement, etc. has happened,
the car has got a very bad
scratch, don't
keep it, guys your bill will be of 500, otherwise these
people will make a bill of 1500 for you, you
can see this guy who is washing my car is a
very good guy, I mean I had got it,
otherwise these people were asking for service charge for this also,
my car was
parked for a long time, I came back here, I
enquired why it has not been done yet, then
these people said that they have not called from your side yet,
I had done all the procedures
but these people had forgotten to call, they
said sorry we will call, then I
called again, saw the inspection officer etc.
also came, so guys I will tell you the bill of these people,
how much is this  The bill was made by him, there were
only minor problems in my car,
so guys you can see this bill, this bill has
increased from Rs 5000 to Rs 10000, these people
loot so much, guys I did
not get the service done from here and so guys if you are getting it done
from here then get it done very carefully
and I will not recommend it at all, so guys we will meet
in the next blog, till then bye